http://www.mugglenet.com/site/privacy

Privacy Policy | MuggleNet
Skip to content
Search for:
Special Projects
Volunteer with Us!
Year in Review
MuggleNet Family
Accio Politics
Alohomora!
The Wizard’s Voice
April Fools’
Special Projects
Volunteer with Us!
Year in Review
MuggleNet Family
Accio Politics
Alohomora!
The Wizard’s Voice
April Fools’
Your Privacy
We respect your privacy. We will never give out your email address without your permission. Please click here to go to the feedback form to contact us.
Content
MuggleNet is the sole owner of all content on this site (excluding all copyrighted material).
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
Mediavine Programmatic Advertising
The Website uses Mediavine to manage all third-party advertising on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website. The cookie may collect information relating to your use of the Website, information about your device such as the device’s IP address and browser type, demographic data and, if you arrived at the Website via a link from a third-party site, the URL of the linking page.
First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/.
Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site.
The Website may collect IP addresses and location information to serve personalized ads and pass it to Mediavine. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You may also visit https://optout.aboutads.info/#/ and https://optout.networkadvertising.org/# to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.
Mediavine partners with the following data processors:
Pubmatic. You may find Pubmatic’s privacy policy through this link. The data collected on the Website may be transferred to Pubmatic and its demand partners for interest-based advertising. Statistical information and other non-cookie technologies (such as eTags and web or browser cache) may be used by third parties on this Website. Browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on these technologies, but you may clear your cache to delete such trackers. Data collected from a particular browser or device may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which such data was collected.
Criteo. You may find Criteo’s privacy policy through this link. The data collected on the Website may be transferred to Criteo and its demand partners for interest-based advertising. Criteo may collect, access, and use non-identifying data to improve the Criteo Technology and other Criteo products, programs, and/or services. This non-identifying data may include on-site user behavior and user/page content data, URLs, statistics, or internal search queries. The non-identifying data are collected through the ad call and stored with a Criteo cookie for a maximum period of 13 months.
Pulsepoint. You may find Pulsepoint’s privacy policy through this link.
LiveRamp. You may find LiveRamp’s privacy policy through this link. When you use the Website, we share information that we may collect from you, such as your email (in hashed, de-identified form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with LiveRamp Inc, and its group companies (‘LiveRamp’). LiveRamp may use a cookie on your browser and match your shared information to their on- and offline marketing databases and those of its advertising partners to create a link between your browser and information in those other databases. This link may be shared by our partners globally for the purpose of enabling interest-based content or advertising throughout your online experience (e.g. cross device, web, email, in-app, etc.) by third parties unaffiliated with our website. These third parties may in turn link further demographic or interest-based information to your browser. To opt out of LiveRamp’s targeted advertising, please go here: https://liveramp.com/opt_out/
RhythmOne. You may view RhythmOne’s privacy policy through this link. RhythmOne uses cookies and similar tracking technologies (such as mobile device identifiers and digital fingerprinting) to provide its services. RhythmOne may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the following webpage: https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
District M. You may find District M’s privacy policy through this link.
YieldMo. You may find YieldMo’s privacy policy through this link. If you want to opt out of receiving interest based ads from Yieldmo or exercise your right under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) to opt-out of the sale of your personal information, you may do so through this link.
The Rubicon Project. You may find Rubicon’s privacy policy through this link. If you want to opt out of receiving interest based ads from Rubicon or exercise your right under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) to opt-out of the sale of your personal information, you may do so through this link. You may also utilize the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page.
Amazon Publisher Services. You may find Amazon Publisher Services’ privacy policy through this link.
AppNexus. You may find the AppNexus privacy policy through this link.
OpenX. You may find OpenX’s privacy policy through this link.
Verizon Media formerly known as Oath. You may find Verizon Media’s privacy policy through this link. You may also utilize the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising.
TripleLift. You may find TripleLift’s privacy policy through this link. To opt out of receiving interest-based advertising (including retargeting) from TripleLift’s services through the use of cookies in your current browser and for more information on what it means to opt-out, please go to www.triplelift.com/consumer-opt-out.
Index Exchange. You may find Index Exchange’s privacy policy through this link. You may also utilize the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising.
Sovrn. You may find Sovrn’s privacy policy through this link.
GumGum. You may find GumGum’s privacy policy through this link. GumGum may (i) use place and use cookies on end users’ browsers or use web beacons to collect information about end users who visit such Publisher Websites and (ii) link such collected end user information to other end user information provided by third parties in order to deliver targeted Advertisements to such end users.
Digital Remedy. You may find Digital Remedy’s privacy policy through this link.
MediaGrid. You may find MediaGrid’s privacy policy through this link. MediaGrid may collect and store information about end-user interactions with this website through cookies, advertising IDS, pixels and server-to-server connections. MediaGrid was receive the following information: the page an End-User has requested and the referring/exit pages; Timestamp information (i.e., the date and time the End-User has visited the page); IP address; mobile device identifier; device model; device operating system; browser type; carrier; gender; age; geolocation (including GPS coordinates); clickstream data; cookie information; first-party identifiers’; and hashed email addresses; demographic and inferred interest information; and post-conversion data (from both online and offline behaviour). Some of this data is gathered from this website and others is gathered from advertisers. MediaGrid uses this data to provide its services. You may also utilize the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising or review their privacy policy for more information.
RevContent – You may find RevContent’s privacy policy through this link. RevContent may collect information about your browser or device, including browser type, IP Address, device type, user agent string, and operating system. RevContent also collects information about the websites you visit through their services, such as date and time of access and specific pages accessed and the content and ads you click on. You may opt-out of any personalization track by opting-out of RevContent’s data collection.
Centro, Inc. – You may find Centro’s privacy policy through this link. You may find opt-out information for Centro’s services through the privacy policy link.
33Across, Inc. – You may find 33Across’s privacy policy through this link. To opt-out of personalized advertising, please visit https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1.
Conversant. LLC – You may find Conversant’s privacy policy through this link. Conversant uses information that does not directly identify you, such as information about your browser type, time and date of visit, your browsing or transaction activity, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, and a unique identifier (such as a cookie string, or a unique advertising identifier provided by your mobile device) during your visits to this and other websites and apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Conversant may use technologies such as cookies and other tracking technologies to collect this information. To learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt-out, you can visit www.youronlinechoices.eu or https://www.networkadvertising.org/.
Follow:
Search for:
Our Commitment
Become a Patron!Upcoming Events
Sun, Oct 11
Dawn French's birthday
Mon, Oct 12
Madison Ford's birthday
Eleanor Columbus's birthday
Katie Bell Imperiused by Madam Rosmerta
Dave Legeno's birthday (RIP)
Harry performs Levicorpus on a sleeping Ron
Wed, Oct 14
Dumbledore shows Harry his memory of Tom Riddle at the orphanage
Fri, Oct 16
Lavender's rabbit Binky dies
More
Quotes
“It’s S-P-E-W. Stands for the Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare.”
#PotterHistory
July 21, 2007 – Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows is released to the world.
Did You Know
Term at Hogwarts begins on September 1.
MuggleNet Archive MuggleNet Archive
Select Month
October 2020  (24)
September 2020  (108)
August 2020  (151)
July 2020  (118)
June 2020  (95)
May 2020  (116)
April 2020  (121)
March 2020  (93)
February 2020  (95)
January 2020  (55)
December 2019  (78)
November 2019  (84)
October 2019  (122)
September 2019  (123)
August 2019  (125)
July 2019  (112)
June 2019  (96)
May 2019  (106)
April 2019  (100)
March 2019  (115)
February 2019  (105)
January 2019  (82)
December 2018  (118)
November 2018  (159)
October 2018  (140)
September 2018  (117)
August 2018  (107)
July 2018  (130)
June 2018  (102)
May 2018  (94)
April 2018  (122)
March 2018  (117)
February 2018  (72)
January 2018  (89)
December 2017  (87)
November 2017  (81)
October 2017  (96)
September 2017  (94)
August 2017  (92)
July 2017  (116)
June 2017  (106)
May 2017  (87)
April 2017  (115)
March 2017  (118)
February 2017  (93)
January 2017  (91)
December 2016  (105)
November 2016  (164)
October 2016  (114)
September 2016  (111)
August 2016  (140)
July 2016  (116)
June 2016  (77)
May 2016  (74)
April 2016  (85)
March 2016  (90)
February 2016  (92)
January 2016  (122)
December 2015  (119)
November 2015  (154)
October 2015  (172)
September 2015  (142)
August 2015  (132)
July 2015  (109)
June 2015  (109)
May 2015  (86)
April 2015  (86)
March 2015  (123)
February 2015  (91)
January 2015  (112)
December 2014  (92)
November 2014  (136)
October 2014  (165)
September 2014  (140)
August 2014  (159)
July 2014  (184)
June 2014  (177)
May 2014  (186)
April 2014  (155)
March 2014  (130)
February 2014  (184)
January 2014  (108)
December 2013  (279)
November 2013  (183)
October 2013  (140)
September 2013  (144)
August 2013  (205)
July 2013  (128)
June 2013  (81)
May 2013  (70)
April 2013  (88)
March 2013  (116)
February 2013  (103)
January 2013  (107)
December 2012  (94)
November 2012  (115)
October 2012  (85)
September 2012  (73)
August 2012  (88)
July 2012  (83)
June 2012  (107)
May 2012  (91)
April 2012  (69)
March 2012  (183)
February 2012  (115)
January 2012  (147)
December 2011  (128)
November 2011  (141)
October 2011  (111)
September 2011  (103)
August 2011  (87)
July 2011  (104)
June 2011  (110)
May 2011  (55)
April 2011  (62)
March 2011  (61)
February 2011  (64)
January 2011  (64)
December 2010  (55)
November 2010  (129)
October 2010  (95)
September 2010  (66)
August 2010  (75)
July 2010  (49)
June 2010  (84)
May 2010  (72)
April 2010  (52)
March 2010  (63)
February 2010  (72)
January 2010  (58)
December 2009  (92)
November 2009  (91)
October 2009  (61)
September 2009  (51)
August 2009  (50)
July 2009  (143)
June 2009  (111)
May 2009  (74)
April 2009  (79)
March 2009  (72)
February 2009  (61)
January 2009  (49)
December 2008  (56)
November 2008  (53)
October 2008  (41)
September 2008  (43)
August 2008  (45)
July 2008  (76)
June 2008  (56)
May 2008  (59)
April 2008  (65)
March 2008  (48)
February 2008  (45)
January 2008  (35)
December 2007  (57)
November 2007  (56)
October 2007  (48)
September 2007  (36)
August 2007  (45)
July 2007  (104)
June 2007  (99)
May 2007  (46)
April 2007  (39)
March 2007  (44)
February 2007  (41)
January 2007  (30)
December 2006  (27)
November 2006  (22)
October 2006  (24)
September 2006  (17)
August 2006  (36)
July 2006  (30)
June 2006  (21)
May 2006  (38)
April 2006  (21)
March 2006  (21)
February 2006  (13)
January 2006  (36)
December 2005  (25)
November 2005  (27)
October 2005  (42)
September 2005  (37)
August 2005  (54)
July 2005  (62)
June 2005  (45)
May 2005  (40)
April 2005  (34)
March 2005  (31)
February 2005  (40)
January 2005  (41)
December 2004  (66)
November 2004  (80)
October 2004  (60)
September 2004  (39)
August 2004  (44)
July 2004  (58)
June 2004  (36)
May 2004  (31)
April 2004  (24)
March 2004  (23)
February 2004  (17)
January 2004  (18)
December 2003  (15)
November 2003  (21)
October 2003  (12)
September 2003  (19)
August 2003  (10)
July 2003  (15)
June 2003  (25)
May 2003  (8)
April 2003  (10)
March 2003  (8)
February 2003  (14)
January 2003  (11)
December 2002  (13)
November 2002  (8)
October 2002  (1)
August 2002  (1)
March 2002  (3)
October 2001  (1)
July 2001  (1)
April 2001  (1)
March 2001  (1)
February 2001  (4)
October 2000  (1)
June 2000  (1)
December 1999  (1)
September 1999  (1)
August 1999  (1)
June 1999  (1)
February 1999  (1)
MuggleNet is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program and Bookshop.org, affiliate advertising programs designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com and bookshop.org.
MuggleNet is an unofficial Harry Potter fansite.Please email us if you have any questions or concerns.© 1999-2020 MuggleNet.com. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy | COPPA Policy | Terms of Use | Feedback
